{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "One shouldn't give up ___ he/she has failed many times.",
      "a": "even if",
      "b": "since",
      "c": "whether",
      "d": "until",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Even if: emphasize that something is true although something else has happened.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ far away you are, you are always in your dearest friends' minds.",
      "a": "Not with standing",
      "b": "Even though",
      "c": "In spite of",
      "d": "No matter how",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- No matter how + adj: regardless of",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The roof fell ___ the anxious father had time to dash into his house to save his baby.",
      "a": "as",
      "b": "after",
      "c": "until",
      "d": "before",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Before: earlier than a particular event or action ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Young ___ he is, the child knows how to assemble a small robot.",
      "a": "if",
      "b": "though",
      "c": "even if",
      "d": "as",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- As...as: used in comparisons ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Everything depends on ___ the decision maker would change his mind.",
      "a": "whether",
      "b": "if",
      "c": "so",
      "d": "so that",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Whether: used when talking about a choice you have to make or about something that is not certain ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "You'd better hurry _________ it seems to rain soon.",
      "a": "but",
      "b": "and",
      "c": "unless",
      "d": "as",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- As: used to state why a particular situation exists or why someone does something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Everyone has no idea ___ far the nearest gas station is from here.",
      "a": "how",
      "b": "what",
      "c": "that",
      "d": "it's",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n\n- How: (+ adjective/adverb) used to emphasize the quality you are mentioning",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "You'll gain the victory ___ you have a strong will in your mind.",
      "a": "until",
      "b": "unless",
      "c": "as well as",
      "d": "as long as",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- As long as: On the condition that",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What the scholar said is strange, ___ it is true.",
      "a": "and but",
      "b": "but and",
      "c": "and yet",
      "d": "yet and",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Yet: used to introduce a fact, situation, or quality that is surprising after what you have just said",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Time passed quickly and one month went by ___ we knew it.",
      "a": "after",
      "b": "before",
      "c": "till",
      "d": "when",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Before: earlier than a particular event or action ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}